KEVIN LAI

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER



EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Full-stack Engineer Escrow Protocol | 2021

- Worked on building launchpad for ICO on Optimism Ethereum(Optimistic Rollup)
- Built DeFi project by using auto-compounding system like Yield Farming Optimizer
- Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js.
- Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.
- Built NFT marketplace forking from Metaplex.

Blockchain Developer

ZILIONIXX MULTICHAINS TECHNOLOGY PTE. LTD. | 2019 - 2020

- Worked on building trading view, swap modal using React, Next, TypeScript, Webs.js, and Subgraph.
- Worked on building Zilionixx chain, ZNX tokenomics
- Worked on building Block explorer and Swapping site.
- Developed automated trading strategies on Uniswap and QuickSwap.
- Built smart contract with solidity and designed unit test with Truffle.
- Implemented and integrated a new end-toend testing suite that reduced regressions by 70%.

ABOUT ME

Mr. Kevin has been collaborating with a variety of companies including small startups and big communities, which has made him intimately familiar with all the stages of the web lifecycle from the initial architecture to final deployment. Recently, he has worked on several cryptocurrency projects piling up great knowledge on blockchain tech. He is also not new to the remote freelancing scene, so he is extremely flexible with his working hours.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science

Swarthmore college

2011 - 2015

- Computer Science, High Honors,
- Artificial Intelligence & Mathematics and statistics.
- Graduated: Nov, 2015; GPA: 3.7

Artificial Intelligence Intern

Singapore Institute of Technology 2017 - 2018

- Artificial Intelligence Course, Statistic Analysis.
- Assistant for Senior AI engineer
- Certificate: Al programming with Python,

KEVIN LAI

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER



EXPERIENCE

Blockchain Developer

Gelato Network | 2019

- Used Flashbots API to fetch block info regarding trading pool and staking.
- Supported limit orders on the Ethereum Mainnet and Polygon (Matic).
- Built smart contract with solidity and deployed using Truffle.
- Worked on building NFT Market Place.
- Created a POC React.js front-end platform for an NFT gallery using Moralis and React.
- Worked on the token distribution and migration from BSC to Polygon network using BscScan, PolygonScan API, and Solidity.

Full-stack Developer

Centro, Inc | 2018 - 2019

- Created a Firebase cloud-function back end with Node.js for the Ellipsis mobile app and web dashboards.
- Constructed an automatic voice call center using Twilio and Node.js together with an NLP API.
- Created a React front-end admin dashboard for complex table data visualization with userfriendly search features.
- Used Google Cloud Platform heavily, namely Google Storage, BigQuery, Speech-to-Text API, and Firebase.

PROJECTS

JuiceBox | Escrow Protocol

https://juicebox.money

Cashcow protocol | Escrow Protocol

https://cashcowprotocol.com

POP Town | Escrow Protocol

https://new.pop.town

Zilionixx | Zilionixx

https://zilionixx.com

Zilionixx Swap | Zilionixx

https://matchaswap.zilionixx.com/

Dongle Trade | Zilionixx

http://dongletrade.com

ZNX scan | Zilionixx

http://znxscan.com

Techspecs | Centro, Inc

https://techspecs.io

GruntApp | Tripcents

Multi-object trackers | SIT

Extractive Text Summarizer + Keywords Identification | SIT

KEVIN LAI

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER



EXPERIENCE

Back-end Developer

Tripcents | 2017 - 2018

- Built back-end APIs using Firebase cloud functions, a real-time database, and cloud messaging.
- Solved a payment integration problem that required high security and accuracy for different user banks. The central payment system was Dwolla and we used Plaid for the connection bridge.
- Integrated various third-party APIs for real estate, flight booking, and reservation.
- Structured the database to optimize all the data in a real-time database using MongoDB on AWS EC2.

Python Developer

Coligo Technologies | 2016

- Working on company main service product and update the legacy product to modern, refactored testable and maintainable product
- Extract all products services, workflows and structures and convert them from legacy old framework (django 1.x) to new modern structure (Flask)
- Designed an ETL to load logs from multiple sources (PostgreSQL, PrefectETL, AWS)

SKILLS

Blockchain Theory	
Solidity	
Solana	
Rust	
Web3	
React	
Javascript	
Typescript	
Node	
Python	
Go	
Tensorflow	
Caffe2	
Machine Learning	
AWS	

CONTACT



+1 (973) 380 0576



kevinvanlet@gmail.com



https://kevinvanlet.wixsite.com/portfolio



Coffeyville, KS 67337, United States